The money from Congressman
Ramon dela Peña's illegal businesses
is being laundered in Casa Fuerte.
Stay here until the situation becomes okay.
- Why did you have to drag me into it?
- The kid asked for your help
while he was having a heart attack.
But what did you do?
- Where's the typewriter?
- How does the darn typewriter work?
You can change your life!
I know how much you loved me.
You got my father blind.
What should I do with it?
Who told you that?
No secret remains hidden forever.
I will kill Liam.
No, Dad! Please.
Dad, please! Not Liam!
- Dad!
- He was brought to Pulang Buhangin.
Liam was abducted.
I treated you like my son.
You gave me hope.
I even forgot that
I was grieving for my wife
because you brought me success.
I trusted you...
because I could see myself in you.
But you're a traitor!
I raised a monster.
I didn't know that
you'd bite the hand that feeds you.
You don't have an ounce of conscience!
Go on and shoot.
Shoot me!
What?
Kill me!
You're evil!
You should die!
You are all talk.
You know me.
My life, my game.
So why don't we play?
Survival of the fittest.
Both our lives are worthless anyway.
Let's see who will get lucky.
Let the bullet judge...
who should stay alive.
Until now, you still want to be in control.
You treat everyone like puppets!
Were you even a good father to Via?
I'm not surprised that
your daughter became evil!
You're a worthless father!
It's too late for the sermon.
I already lost a lot.
Now, I want you to get lost!
Are you serious, Lando?
You brought a typewriter?
Take it easy.
I brought a gun too.
Did you know that this typewriter is magical?
Did you also know that I once died?
But because of this, I came back to life.
Via, did you know that
this thing can change your life?
You can wish whatever you want.
All you have to do is write it
using this typewriter.
This story should have a magical typewriter.
The hero will return to the past,
and he will use the typewriter to do that.
I will never let you use me again!
Your wickedness has to end!
Okay, then.
I'm setting you free.
Go on.
Go ahead! Kill me!
I'm not scared of you! I'm not scared to die!
Kill me now!
Dad!
Liam, Liam.
Liam, Liam...
Liam, wake up. Wake up!
Don't be like this. Please, please.
Liam, Liam!
Liam.
Love...
I'm so sorry, my love.
I'm so sorry.
Liam, my love.
Love!
Help!
Help! Please, help us!
Love...
Liam!
No, no, no, no, no.
If you really are magical...
then show me.
I love you so much, Liam.
You are my life.
I will die if I lose you.
If I have to take you away from death,
I will.
You're only mine, Liam.
What did you do, Via?
Joyce...
I won't let my dad kill you.
I will catch the bullet for you.
We will be together.
This is what I want.
This is my wish.
Where am I?
What's this? Is this another dream?
So, what if she doesn't like me?
What if she does?
Take a leap of faith.
I love you.
You're supposed to pick Dexter up!
Where were you?
Liam was telling the truth.
The typewriter is truly magical.
We did have a life together.
Joyce, please forgive me.
It is all my fault.
I didn't mean it, Joyce. Please, forgive me.
Liam, what are you doing?
What are you talking about?
What's happening?
Liam?
Dex!
For the third time,
your story will change, Liam...
And even those who are dear to you.
This is not what you wanted.
So brace yourself
for what can happen in return.
Where am I?
Where are we?
I won't let my Dad kill you.
Via.
Via! Via!
I will take the bullet for you.
Via. Via.
We'll be together.
Via, Via, why?
Why not?
This is what I want.
This is my wish.
I love you, Liam.
Via, don't talk like that.
Via, Via, Via.
Via.
Via, Via, Via, Via.
Via?
Lando.
What are you and Via doing here?
That bullet was supposed to be for you.
Lando!
Get Via.
Sir...
I'm sorry, but this is already out of hand.
That's your daughter.
I don't want to get involved.
You're already worthless.
Via, I remember I rushed you to the hospital.
You also collapsed in the hospital.
What my dad did to you was really bad.
But thank you, Liam.
Thank you for saving me.
If it wasn't for you...
it would have been worse.
The doctor told me I could no longer walk.
Why did you take the bullet for me?
After what I did to you, Via?
I don't know, either.
When we were there...
I wasn't thinking about
the painful events.
All I know is...
I love you.
Liam...
Liam, I still love you.
Don't worry.
We're safe here.
I asked Queenie for help.
We're in her house in the province.
I need to take you away from my dad.
We need to hide.
I'm sorry, Via.
I know what Ramon can do to get back at me.
I only want to make sure
that my loved ones are safe.
I need to see them.
Liam.
Aunt Tess is safe.
And Joyce too.
How did you know?
Queenie is monitoring them,
and she keeps me updated
every chance she gets.
Can you please believe me
just this once, Liam?
Trust me.
When you chose Joyce over me,
I knew...
I could no longer decide for you.
The doors are not locked, Liam.
You can leave.
But you said it yourself.
You know what my dad can do.
He won't stop as long as he's free.
I only want them to be safe, Via.
I won't leave.
I won't also leave you in that condition.
Thank you.
Joyce.
Liam...
Liam is my husband.
Dex...
Dex, my son...
- My son.
- Joyce, Joyce.
Joyce.
Joyce...
Liam...
Joyce, you're awake now.
Joyce, you're already awake.
Joyce, you're awake.
I'm glad you're finally awake.
Joyce, look at me.
What's the last thing you remember?
Because...
when you left me at the coffee shop...
we received a report.
They saw you unconscious
beside the lifeless body
of Lando Nakpil in a parking lot.
Joyce...
what really happened?
I confirmed everything that was happening
was all real.
I had to confirm everything
before asking for your help.
But it was too late when I got there, Hans.
Because...
Because Ramon was about to shoot Liam
but Via saved him.
She took the bullet.
Yes, they have a hospital record, but...
after that, Liam and Via went missing.
What?
What do you mean they're missing?
What's going on? Why are we here?
We're like rats hiding in a hole.
Why is this happening?
I'm also not used to this look, Madam.
It feels strange.
Oh, come on! I even left my lipstick
because we were in a hurry.
Oh.
I'm glad I was able to bring this.
Madam...
The gold you are wearing might melt
and turn you into an Oscars statuette
for Best Actress.
Don't you feel the heat?
You talk too much.
Mind your own business.
And look at this.
This is my investment.
I'm glad I brought it.
They won't get stolen.
Your mom is taking it out on me again.
Mommy, please.
What matters is that we're safe.
Listen to your daughter, Joanne.
Oh, wow.
Are you ganging up on me?
That's what you're good at.
Taking each other's sides.
You're both stupid.
You think we're safe
because we're in a safe house.
But the truth is, we're in a safe house
because we're not safe!
That's the truth!
Madam, you better take off your jewelry.
It reflects the sunlight.
That's why you're getting
even more hot-headed.
You shine like a disco ball at noon.
There's a heatwave across the country.
You might suffer from heat stroke.
Complaining won't do us any good, Joanne.
We'll stay here.
No one is stopping you from leaving.
- Hans.
- Auntie.
Oh? What's the matter?
Aunt Joanne wants to go out.
Aunt, it's dangerous to go against someone
like Ramon dela Peña.
So I hope you stay put.
I don't want you to end up like Intoy.
Luckily, we found him alive in your house.
You know what, Hans,
I'm not only scared for us.
I'm also scared for Liam.
No mother can be at peace without knowing
where her son could be or if he's safe.
I'll make sure
that you'll reunite with your family.
I promise you that.
Thank you.
Thank you, Hans.
I'll leave you for now.
I also need to talk to the police.
Okay.
Mom.
Joyce...
Thank you.
Mom, I believe it now.
I now believe what you saw...
what Liam was saying...
I now believe what I saw
in my dreams, mom.
Thank you.
It's so nice to hear you call me "Mom".
I'm sure Liam will be glad.
I wish he was here.
Don't worry.
I will take care of it.
What do you mean by that?
You're making me nervous, Joyce.
Joyce...
Intoy.
Intoy, I'm now convinced.
I now believe what you and Liam told me.
I now believe that the typewriter is magical.
I saw my past life.
I saw my previous life with Liam.
Our life with our son, Dex.
I saw how Liam used the typewriter
to change everything.
Joyce...
Do you know where the typewriter is?
Lando took it from me.
That typewriter is so powerful.
It's dangerous that it is in the wrong hands.
I saw Via use it.
I saw how she used it
to bring Liam back to life.
I saw it...
But I wasn't able to get it.
The typewriter was left at Pulang Buhangin.
What if someone else takes it?
How can we get it?
What?
You can't leave this place anymore.
But I can.
In the name of Dior, Gucci,
and holy Versace...
Please take care of me.
Okay.
Aren't you Via's assistant?
What are you doing here?
Me?
What am I doing here?
That's what I ask myself, too.
Looks like I have an existential crisis.
Tell me the truth.
What?
You're spying on us, aren't you?
Where's Via?
Where's Liam?
Miss Via?
Who is Via?
Don't make me force you.
You want the easy way or the hard way?
Tell me where they are.
Miss Via.
That Via.
Of course! She's at...
At...
Look over there!
Hey!
Your life got ruined because of me...
Via...
You don't deserve me, Via.
I'll be honest with you.
I got mad for what you did to me...
For what you and Joyce did.
You don't know the date today, do you?
Eight years ago today...
We met on that bridge.
Liam, tell me.
That day, should I have just
jumped off the bridge?
So I wouldn't be hurting like this?
That's what you're telling me right now.
That I shouldn't have met you
because if we didn't meet,
our life wouldn't be this messy.
A year before that day,
my mom took her own life.
My mom killed herself, Liam.
I came to a point...
where I wished...
to die.
I wanted to die, too.
Via...
Until I met you.
You made me feel that
I still deserve to be loved...
That I still have a purpose to live.
That's why it hurts so much, Liam.
The reason I'm living
is also the reason I'm slowly dying.
Now you're telling me
that you should have died?
That's so selfish, Liam.
You're being selfish.
Via, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
All your suffering will end.
I'll get better.
And then, you can leave me.
Go eat.
Love is not perfect, Via.
What do you mean?
It's not always right.
That's why we make mistakes because of love.
But at the end of the day,
one must be brave enough
to correct all those mistakes...
still for love.
Still...
love is an act of bravery.
You're right.
You're such a stupid, stupid,
pretty rich girl, Via.
Chasing after a guy who obviously
doesn't love you.
Trapped in a wheelchair, lost in the woods.
Wake up.
The things we do for love.
As you say, love is an act of bravery.
I hope I'm not interrupting.
Did you already find the typewriter, Dad?
You really are my daughter.
I'm not surprised that you're still alive.
You called from a faraway land
just to ask about the typewriter.
Ridiculous.
Won't a laptop suffice, Via?
Can you be serious, Dad?
Don't forget that you did me wrong.
You shot me.
Who was stupid enough to take the bullet?
Don't be rude.
I found a way to stop Liam
from messing with you.
I'm not as stupid as you think.
You did that for your own selfish reason.
Where are you?
I'm also not that stupid, Dad.
Why would I tell you?
You'll kill Liam.
Did you find it?
Who's that?
Did they find the typewriter?
Not yet!
You have really gone insane!
Who did I take after?
Find the typewriter, Dad.
I will tell you where to bring and leave it.
I will tell you where we are
once you find it.
What kind of game is this?
Find the typewriter.
I need to find it!
Where are you and Liam?
It's not enough
that I brought you back to life, Liam.
I will find a way...
to take Joyce out of your life.
Via.
Via!
Why didn't you wake me up?
Careful.
Okay.
What happened?
I tried to wake you up because
I needed to use the bathroom.
But I fell.
Sorry, did I wake you up?
No, but you had me worried.
Sorry.
Oh, ouch! Ouch!
Bro, please watch where you're going.
You're gross.
Gross? Wow.
You think you're so handsome?
I'm sorry. I was just surprised.
Bro...
Do you have food with you?
I haven't eaten since dinner.
So, midnight snack?
You haven't had your midnight snack?
What's that?
My stomach hurts already.
It's rumbling.
Like that, and then...
Bro, look at me.
What are you looking for?
Nothing.
That's how life is, bro.
We search for things that are...
already gone.
Most of the time,
we lose some things because of our choices.
You're just hungry.
- Here.
- Bro.
Get some midnight snack.
Wait, I don't have...
Bro, can I have it?
- Go on.
- Bro...
Thank you.
Thank you for this, bro.
This means a lot.
But don't you ever steal my stuff.
- They're mine...
- I don't have any intentions.
I'll just count this to see what it can buy...
Go on.
Popcorn and lechon.
Facing both charges,
former Congressman Ramon dela Peña
remains at large,
but we won't stop until we find him.
Evidence gathered shows that Ramon dela Peña
is behind the death of his former personnel,
Lando Nakpil.
We encourage the public to inform the police
if they have information
that can help our search.
Because this man is extremely dangerous.
I knew it! We're not safe here!
And to you, Ramon dela Peña,
your days are numbered.
Sir, we already found him.
Did you find Liam?
- No.
- Darn it! What did you find?
The warehouse.
Here are the toiletries that you requested.
You need it more...
To clean up your son's name!
You're way out of line.
Can't you be a little considerate?
I don't even know where my son is,
or if he's okay.
Don't you have mercy?
Why would I have mercy?
Whatever happens to him,
your son deserves it!
I don't even care about him!
He deserves whatever will happen to him!
- Mom!
- You're so mean!
Take back what you said!
- Take it back!
- No!
Take it back! My son is not a bad person!
- Madam, that's enough.
- Mom!
Please!
Please.
Fighting won't do any good!
Dad is right, Mom.
We should not waste our energy
in useless fights like this.
We all want one thing.
For all of us to be safe.
That's it!
Mommy, please listen.
No one will die if you cooperate.
Just this once, Mom. Please.
Suit yourself.
Joanne.
- Dad.
- No.
I got it.
Mom, I'm sorry.
Joanne!
Joanne, I'm blind. Where are you?
I'm not here.
Joanne...
Did you follow me here to lecture me, too?
Then do the same thing to me.
We both have shortcomings as parents.
If only I didn't get addicted to drugs...
If only I had prioritized your needs first...
I wasn't a good husband to you, Joanne.
I hope someday you can forgive me.
I feel bad that...
I'm now blind.
But God knows...
God knows how much I want
to hug my wife and daughter.
I still love you, Jo.
Nothing has changed.
I lost my sight,
but my love for you and Joyce remains.
I'm scared.
I'm scared of what can happen
to our daughter, Edmond.
Nothing bad will happen, Joanne.
We're strong.
Let's work together.
Lord...
I don't know what's happening to my son.
I also don't know where he is.
I hope my son is okay wherever he is.
Tess.
Lord, Lord...
I want Liam to be here.
Why did you send this man?
You could have sent a guardian angel instead.
Why?
I'll add security here to watch over you.
Danilo, don't worry about me.
Find Liam.
I also hired a private investigator.
He's already moving.
I'm just being careful
because I don't want Ramon
to trace Liam through me.
Promise me that our son
will come home to me.
That Liam will be fine.
Tess...
I wasn't able to fight for you before.
Now, I will do everything
to protect you and Liam.
Forgive me.
I wasn't as brave as your son.
You know what...
Liam isn't just brave.
He's also kind-hearted.
He taught me...
that we don't have to stay in the dark.
We can always choose the good thing.
Danilo, whatever happened between us
in the past...
I forgive you.
Oh, no!
No!
Hard no!
You.
Looks like you want to take advantage.
We're okay now.
Tess, thank you.
Thank you too, for everything, Danilo.
- I love you so much.
- Mom, I love you so much.
If a couple loves each other,
they will face problems together.
I wish I didn't let anger
get the better of me.
I wish we had dealt with our problem
with Dex together.
I love you so much, Joyce.
I love you so much, Liam.
Let's go back to our old life.
Dex, my son...
Mom's already in Paris.
I've fulfilled my lifelong dream.
Too bad, your dad and I
didn't fulfill it together.